My names are Chief Progress Newerdie.
The people standing beside me:
this is my sister,
these are my brothers - all of them are my brothers.
The last one is the PRO of the community.
Amen.
Lets clap for Jesus Christ!
My testimony goes like this: in January 2016, I was shot.
After they shot me, they shot others – 10 people in number.
They shot me in back of my head.
The Navy there rushed me to Yenagoa and from there, to Abuja.
I was in a state of coma in a hospital, for three weeks.
My people thought I had died; everybody lost hope.
It was even posted on the internet that I deserved to die!
But, by the special grace of God I made it through!
Clap for Jesus!
I was with the Anointed Sticker when they shot me; it was close to my body.
People who are familiar with AK 47 will know that
if somebody shoots you in the head with one, you will die -
but by the special grace of God, I lived.
Chief Progress Neverdie & Friends
Emmanuel TV Testimony
After I made it through the coma, the doctors said they could not remove the bullet from my head.
I was referred to India after undergoing three surgeries in Abuja that did not work.
Then, I could not move so they bought a wheelchair for me; I could not do anything.
It was then, they referred me to India.
After they referred me to India, they discharged me to a hotel;
in the hotel, I saw Prophet T.B. Joshua praying on Emmanuel TV.
While you were in the hotel you were watching Emmanuel TV?
Yes.
And you saw man of God praying?
Yes, my faith was built up and I said that I wanted to touch the television.
I asked those around to help me and they did.
When I placed my hand on the television and prayed along with Prophet T.B. Joshua -
my brothers and sisters, wonders have not come to an end!
Chief Progress Neverdie & Friends
Emmanuel TV Testimony
After the prayer, I began to vomit.
I vomited anything I put in my mouth.
My people were scared.
The bullet that the doctors could not remove came out by itself!
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for the miracle working God!
Our Lord is good.
You've heard a wonderful testimony.
Our brother still has a lot to say, but he is so exited at this moment...
This is the bullet - you can see it on the board.
This is my head.
This is exactly the spot the bullet came from on its own?
Yes.
You had three operations to have the bullet removed - all to no avail?
But after you prayed along with man of God on Emmanuel TV the bullet came out on its own?
Yes.
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for the miracle working God!
This is me on the photo.
One moment, sir.
This was at the time you were hospitalized?
Yes, this photo was taken when I was hospitalized in Abuja.
While I was on the wheelchair, I was wondering what would I do.
This was the first miracle - God was to finish what He had begun.
I asked my sister to bring me to Lagos and she did.
So, when I came I said, "God of Prophet T.B. Joshua, You are the One who created me -
not with a wheelchair; a wheelchair is not my portion."
I stood up and I told my sister to give the hospital their wheelchair back.
Chief Progress Neverdie & Friends
Emmanuel TV Testimony
He said that after he had prayed along with the man of God on Emmanuel TV, the bullet came out by itself,
without any surgical operation.
He flew to Lagos but because of the crowd he could not enter the church.
While the man of God was praying, he prayed along with him at the auditorium.
Then he said to God, "This wheelchair is not for me. I want to get out of this wheelchair and walk."
That is how the miracle happened.
Since then he is walking on his legs without using the wheelchair.
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for the miracle working God.
Now, for the benefit of the listeners, we want you to turn your head and show us the spot where the bullet was.
This is the spot.
When somebody shoots you in the head, you will die.
But I made it.
To God be the glory.
We rejoice with you greatly for having you rescued from the shackles of death.
Through your prayer while watching Emmanuel TV, right now you are healed and healthy.
Now, could you tell us - what word of advice you have for those who are listening to you,
concerning what the Lord Jesus Christ can do because distance is not a barrier.
People of God: what you are hearing is real.
What I want to say is:
2 Kings 2:19-21 says the land was glittering, the people said the land was pleasant
but the water is bad and the land is barren.
Elisha healed the land with salt.
The man of God has the power to heal our land with the Word.
Chief Progress Neverdie & Friends
Emmanuel TV Testimony
Now, we thank God Almighty for what He has done in your life.
We certainly rejoice with you that the Lord has bestowed upon you the healing.
As you go and make His Word the standard for your life, we pray that your miracle remain permanent,
in Jesus' name.
Amen!